<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<i18n baseKey="m.order.document.preferences" lcid="en_GB">
	<key id="edition-form-title">"Orders" module preferences</key>
	<key id="orderconfirmednotificationuser">users notified of new orders</key>
	<key id="orderconfirmednotificationuser-help">The recipients selected here will be notified for each new order paid foror pending payment confirmation.</key>
	<key id="disablecoupons">deactivate the coupons</key>
	<key id="disablecoupons-help">This option disables the display of the coupon input forms in the frontoffice.</key>
	<key id="orderprocessclosedbegindate">'shop closed' start date</key>
	<key id="orderprocessclosedbegindate-help">Start date for the ordering process to be closed.</key>
	<key id="orderprocessclosedenddate">'shop closed' end date</key>
	<key id="orderprocessclosedenddate-help">End date for the ordering process to be suspended.</key>
	<key id="orderprocessclosed">closed</key>
	<key id="orderprocessclosed-help">The ordering process is temporarily suspended. If this field's value is 'Yes',then the ordering process is suspended, regardless of the dates displayed above.</key>
	<key id="orderprocessclosedmessage">'shop closed' message</key>
	<key id="orderprocessclosedmessage-help">This message, from the basket page, tells the customers that the ordering process is suspended.</key>
	<key id="orderprocesscloseddatemessage">'shop closed' message</key>
	<key id="orderprocesscloseddatemessage-help">This message, displayed on the basket page, tells the customers of a planned closure. The markers {beginDate} and {endDate} will respectively be replaced by the start date and the end date for the closure.</key>
	<key id="orderprocessallowedcustomer">authorised customers</key>
	<key id="orderprocessallowedcustomer-help">Choose the customers authorised to place orders while the shop is closed.</key>
	<key id="enablecommentreminder">activate the reminder</key>
	<key id="commentreminderperiod">days before the reminder</key>
	<key id="commentreminderreference">reference date</key>
	<key id="commentreminderselection">product selection</key>
	<key id="commentremindercount">maximum product count for reminder</key>
	<key id="commentremindercount-help">This is the maximum product count for which the reminder notification will invite comments on the products.</key>
	<key id="commentreminderperiod-help">This is the delay (in days) after which a reminder is sent.</key>
	<key id="commentreminderreference-help">This is the date after which the delay is applied.</key>
	<key id="commentreminderselection-help">In the products selection mode, a reminder notification will invite comments on the products.</key>
	<key id="document-name">preferences</key>
	<key id="enablecommentreminder-help">If activated, sends a notification some time after an order has been placed to invite the customer to comment on the products that he or she has bought.</key>
</i18n>